

Knowledgeable Senior Accounts Receivable Specie list with 11+years' experience leading AR teams in a fast-paced department. Expert knowledge of Microsoft Office software and specialist accountancy programs, including Xero and Sage Business Cloud. Results-driven and dedicated work ethic with the ability to work efficiently and precisely under acute time pressure.

**Professional Experience** 

# Senior Accounts Receivable Specialist

ARAG North America, Des Moines, IA February 2014 - Present

- Perform accounts audits to check that they are correctly set up with the appropriate premium application
- ♦ Oversee accounts receivable files and prepare 5500forms
- Investigate and reconcile account irregularities and discrepancies and make recommendations to prevent a recurrence
- Liaise with clients regularly to obtain necessary documentation and filesand resolve instances of underpayment
- Mentor new starters and provide training on accounts receivable principles, processes, and policies

### Accounts Receivable Clerk

Lutheran Services in Iowa, Des Moines, IA July 2009 - February 2014

- Completed data entry tasks and sales journals quickly and accurately
- Prepared for and assisted with external financial audits
- Generated client invoices for medical servicesand facilitated insurance claims
- Reviewed and improved the company's accounts receivable processes to improve billing efficiency by 35%

321 Main Road, Des Moines, IA 76543 d,parry@email,com (765) 432-1098

## Education

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration

College of Business and Public
Administration,
Drake University. Des Moines, IA
September 2005 - June 2009

# Key Skills

- Articulate written and verbal communicator
- · Excellent mathematical ability
- · Detai I-oriented
- Outstanding time-management, prioritization,and multi-tasking skills
- Data entry
- Comprehensive knowledge of advanced Excel functions

## Certifications

♦ I OEM Accounts Receivable Certification